const questions = [
	{
		question: 'Which of the following is a microeconomic concept?',
		choices: [
			'stock exchange',
			'personal finance',
			'market failure',
			'trust fund',
		],
		correctAnswer: 2,
	},
	{
		question:
			'The concept of diminishing return explains which of the following phenomena?',
		choices: [
			'A worker cannot maintain the same level of output after long hours of work',
			'When the price of a good rises, people will buy less of it',
			'Company will benefit more from buying captial goods than hiring additional workers',
			'A worker will be less producitive if he is paid less',
		],
		correctAnswer: 0,
	},
	{
		question:
			'A farmer invested in his wheat farm and made a profit of $100. Which one of the following is the opportunity cost?',
		choices: [
			'Soil needs time to heal from the farming',
			'Wheat lost due to pests',
			'Money spent on fertilizer',
			'Profit from planting a different crop',
		],
		correctAnswer: 3,
	},
	{
		question:
			'Should a wealthy country ever trade with a poor country that is less productive in every industry?',
		choices: [
			'No, because of the concept of absolute advantage',
			'Yes, because of the concept of comparative advantage',
			'Yes, because of the concept of absolute advantage',
			'Yes, because of the concept of diminishing return',
		],
		correctAnswer: 0,
	},
	{
		question: 'Which of the following is not shifter of demand curve?',
		choices: ['population', 'income', 'future expectation', 'technology'],
		correctAnswer: 3,
	},
	{
		question:
			'Which of the following is an example of a non-excludable rivalry good?',
		choices: ['public good', 'club good', 'natural resources', 'private good'],
		correctAnswer: 2,
	},
	{
		question:
			'Which of the following concept explains why transfer trip so much cheaper than direct trip?',
		choices: [
			'diminishing returns',
			'price discrimmination',
			'concept of time as a resource',
			'ecnonomics of scale',
		],
		correctAnswer: 1,
	},
	{
		question:
			'When the price of peanut increases by 20 percent, the quantity demanded of jelly decreases by 40 percent. What is the cross-price elasticity of the two goods?',
		choices: ['0.2', '-0.2', '-2', '2'],
		correctAnswer: 2,
	},
	{
		question:
			'Which of the following is the least likely way to increase the amount of healthcare that people provide their children?',
		choices: [
			'reduce the distance traveled to get healthcare',
			'subsidize healthcare',
			'provide coupons for free healthcare',
			'increase the price of healthcare',
		],
		correctAnswer: 0,
	},
	{
		question:
			'Which one of the following is not a reason why we study microecnonomics?',
		choices: [
			'determine how goods can be best allocated for various goods and services',
			'determine the best course of action for individual firms',
			'understand the principle of demand and supply to be able to keep the company afloat',
			'understand the principle of economics on a individual level to be able to make better financial decisions',
		],
		correctAnswer: 3,
	},
	{
		question: 'Which of the following is an example of negative externality?',
		choices: [
			'Drinking too much coffee can make a person feel ill',
			'Too many new firms opening causes existing firms to lose profit',
			'Opening of a new factory causes the neighborhood real estate value to drop',
			'A new technology allows some firms to make more profit but not all firms',
		],
		correctAnswer: 2,
	},
	{
		question: 'What Microeconomics is about?',
		choices: [
			'Study of Business Environment',
			'Study of the Economy at Micro Level',
			'Study of financial position of the economy',
			'None of the above',
		],
		correctAnswer: 1,
	},
	{
		question:
			'Which one of the following is not an example of non-price competition?',
		choices: [
			'Charge less for specific services',
			'Advertising',
			'Membership card',
			'Loyalty Program',
		],
		correctAnswer: 0,
	},
	{
		question: 'While in Perfect Competition',
		choices: [
			'Input prices are given',
			'Buyers are independent',
			'Firms are price taker',
			'None of the above',
		],
		correctAnswer: 0,
	},
	{
		question:
			'Oligopolies can end up looking like competitive markets if the number of firms is',
		choices: [
			'small and they all cooperate',
			'small and they do not cooperate',
			'large and they all cooperate',
			'large and they do not cooperate',
		],
		correctAnswer: 3,
	},
	{
		question: 'Comparative advantage is based on',
		choices: ['dollar price', 'labor cost', 'capitol cost', 'opportunity cost'],
		correctAnswer: 3,
	},
	{
		question:
			'If a company in a perfect competition is making zero profit, what should it do?',
		choices: [
			'Increase its price to increase revenue',
			'Shut down',
			'Advertise its products',
			'None of the above',
		],
		correctAnswer: 3,
	},
	{
		question: 'In a market economy',
		choices: [
			'demand determines supply and supply, in turn, determines prices',
			'supply determines demand and demand, in turn, determines prices',
			'supply and demand determine prices and prices, in turn, allocate the economyâ€™s scarce resources',
			'the allocation of scarce resources determines prices and prices, in turn, determine supply and demand',
		],
		correctAnswer: 2,
	},
	{
		question: 'If demand is price inelastic, then',
		choices: [
			'buyers do not respond much to a change in price',
			'buyers respond substantially to a change in price, but the response is very slow',
			'buyers do not respond much to advertising, fads, or general changes in tastes',
			'the demand curve is very flat',
		],
		correctAnswer: 0,
	},
	{
		question: 'What type of economic system is the United States following?',
		choices: ['command', 'absolute', 'market', 'traditional'],
		correctAnswer: 2,
	},
	{
		question:
			'Which of the following is not a type of modern market structure?',
		choices: [
			'monopoly',
			'international market',
			'oligopoly',
			'monopolistic competition',
		],
		correctAnswer: 1,
	},
	{
		question: 'Market failure is the inability of',
		choices: [
			'some unregulated markets to allocate resources efficiently',
			'a market to establish an equilibrium price',
			'buyers to place a value on the good or service',
			'buyers to interact harmoniously with sellers in the market',
		],
		correctAnswer: 0,
	},
	{
		question:
			'Within a country, the domestic price of a product will equal the world price if',
		choices: [
			'trade restrictions are imposed on the product',
			'the country chooses to import, but not export, the product',
			'the country chooses to export, but not import, the product',
			'the country allows free trade',
		],
		correctAnswer: 3,
	},
	{
		question:
			'Which one of the following is not a reason why companies give student discount?',
		choices: [
			'Discount is a form of advertising in itself',
			'Obtaining the royalty of younger customers',
			'Students may not buy the product otherwise, captures wider range of customer',
			'They care about students',
		],
		correctAnswer: 2,
	},
	{
		question:
			'Which of the following best describes the concept of average total cost?',
		choices: [
			'The cost that does not change per unit of output',
			'The cost of producting one unit of output',
			'The cost of producting one more unit of output',
			'The cost that varies as output changes for every unit of output',
		],
		correctAnswer: 1,
	},
];

export default questions;
